A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 87), 1978-1987; 1980-1986; 1.13; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 record storage boxes; 32 standard record storage boxes - Box R2364-R2395.
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Columbia University - Oral history and women's studies conference, 1983-1986 S (Box R2383)
      - Community School of Performing Arts - Chinese musicians, 1981-1983 (Box R2383)
      - Connecticut Commission on the Arts - State arts agencies study, 1982-1984 1986 (Box R2383)
      - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1982-1986 S (Box R2384)
      - Council of Chief State School Officers - Art education, 1984-1986 (Box R2384)
      - Council on Foundations - "We don't fund media", 1983-1984 (Box R2384)
      - Editorial Projects in Education - Literacy, 1981-1986 (Box R2385)
      - Feminist Press - American literature, 1983-1986 (Box R2385)
      - Film Arts Foundation - "A legacy of hearts and hands", 1983-1986 (Box R2385)
      - Haleakala, Inc. - Touring program, 1984-1986 (Box R2385)
      - Hampshire College - American studies conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2385)
      - Harlem School of the Arts, 1979-1986 (Box R2385)
      - Harvard University - Dictionary of unconventional Russian, 1983-1985 1987 (Box R2386)
      - Hykes, David, 1979-1986 (Box R2386)
      - Johns Hopkins University - New West Indies guide, 1984-1986 S (Box R2386)
      - Long Bow Group - China conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2386)
      - Modern Language Association - Faculty exchange, 1983-1986 (Box R2386)
      - Morehouse College - Afro-American journalists, 1977-1984 1986 [S] (Box R2386)
      - Opera America - Conference, 1982-1985 S (Box R2386)
      - Organization of American Historians - High school teachers, 1983-1985 (Box R2387)
      - Palfi, Stephen, 1979-1984 (Box R2387)
      - Southeast Banking Corporation Foundation - Florida's culture in the nineties, 1984-1986 (Box R2387)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Visual artists-in-residence, 1977-1984 S (Box R2387)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Visual artists-in-residence (SUPP. MATERIAL) (Box R2388)
      - State University of New York - Television and the Arts, 1975-1986 (Box R2388)
      - Sundance Institute for Film & Television - Production assistance fund, 1982-1986 (Box R2388)
      - Tulane University - Jazz archives, 1980-1986 (Box R2389)
      - University of Arizona - "Visions of landscape", 1982-1984 1986 (Box R2389)
      - University of California - Historical studies, 1975-1985 (Box R2389)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Humanities studies, 1982-1985 (Box R2389)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Humanities studies (SUPPL. MATERIAL) (Box R2390)
      - Wake Forest University - Visual artists-in-residence, 1974-1984 (Box R2390)
      - Winston-Salem - Visual artists-in-residence, 1977-1985 (Box R2390)
      - Women's Interart Center - "Amoskeag, Amoskeag" film, 1982-1984 S (Box R2390)
      - Wuorinen, Charles, 1978-1984 (Box R2390)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Minnesota - Agricultural economics (also Arch 2), 1931-1984 (Box R2391)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Guerra, Oswaldo F., 1982-1984 1986 (Box R2391)
      - Laniado, Ruthie N., 1982-1986 (Box R2391)
    - Brazil - University Development, UD
      - Agreements, 1971-1973 1975 1982-1983 (Box R2391)
      - University of Bahia - Health projects, 1978-1984 S (Box R2391)
      - University of Bahia - Regional disease center, 1979-1984 (Box R2391)
  - Chile, 309
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Reyes, Juan G., 1984-1986 (Box R2392)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Gomez de Leon Cruces, Jose, 1982-1984 (Box R2392)
  - England, 401
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - New, Roger R.C., 1983-1986 (Box R2392)
      - University of Southampton - Epidemiology survey, 1982-1985 (Box R2392)
  - Scotland, 405
    - Scotland - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of Edinburgh - Scaife, 1984-1985 (Box R2392)
  - India, 464
    - India - Medical Sciences, A
      - All-India Institute - Reproduction symposium, 1978 1981-1982 (Box R2392)
  - China, 601
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Lin Wan-Lu, 1982-1984 (Box R2392)
      - Ren, Yung-Feng, 1983-1984 (Box R2392)
      - Shen Yu-Fei, 1983-1984 (Box R2392)
      - Yan, Yuan Chang, 1982-1984 (Box R2392)
  - Japan, 609
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Taketo, Taruko, 1982-1984 (Box R2392)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kim, Doo-sub, 1983-1984 (Box R2392)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Ramathibodi Faculty of Medicine, 1972-1984 [S] (Box R2392)
      - Ramathibodi Faculty of Medicine (SUPPL. MATERIAL) (Box R2393)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Rice and Corn/Sorghum, 1965-1983 [S] (Box R2393)
      - Rice and Corn/Sorghum (SUPPL. MATERIAL) (Box R2394)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Depari, Edward, 1978-1985 (Box R2394)
      - Hadiyono, Johana E.P., 1977-1985 (Box R2394)
  - Italy, 751
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Iela, Luisa, 1982-1985 (Box R2394)
  - Finland, 787
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kulomaa, Markus S., 1980-1985 (Box R2394)
  - Poland, 789
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kolasa, Jerzy, 1982-1983 (Box R2394)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Hayat, Nulifer A., 1984-1985 (Box R2394)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Barami, Shalom, 1981-1984 (Box R2394)
  - Program and Policy - Humanities, 911
    - Program and Policy - Humanities, E
      - Boyer, M. Christine, 1982-1985 (Box R2394)
      - Dye, Nancy S., 1981-1984 (Box R2395)
      - Feinberg, Joel, 1980-1983 (Box R2395)
      - Fuegi, John, 1981-1984 1986 (Box R2395)
      - Hedrick, Joan D., 1982-1984 (Box R2395)
      - Hirshson, Stanley, 1980-1984 (Box R2395)
      - Suleiman, Susan R., 1982-1985 (Box R2395)
  - Program and Policy - Arts, 925
    - Program and Policy - Arts - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Center for New Television - Sandin, 1980-1984 (Box R2395)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corp. - Jonas, 1980-1985 (Box R2395)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Viola, 1980-1984 (Box R2395)